Hey Vogue, I'm Kendall Jenner and this is what I wear in a week.
So this I'd say is my everyday kind of running errands, running around town look.
I am wearing a little black tee by Sunday's Best.
My jeans are Kate, they are actually probably my most favorite jeans ever.
They're like the best fit and super long, which is hard for me to find.
I don't usually find jeans that are long enough for my legs.
So these are perfect.
They're at the perfect high waist, mid waist spot.
And then my red sweater is as well Kate.
There's a common theme going on.
I love Kate, but I love the pop of red.
I kind of get cold all the time.
So I love having something on me where I can warm myself back up.
And then my loafers are the row.
They're this really pretty like brown with almost like a hint of red in them.
I love these loafers, and they're actually super comfortable.
I feel like I can wear them everywhere.
I don't ever leave the house or a hotel without a pair of sunglasses.
I just feel safe behind them or something.
So I have to have my sunnies.
These are vintage.
They're Gucci.
Love these guys.
And then last but not least, I'm gonna add a bag.
This is a brand-new Bottega bag that I'm loving right now.
Good guy.
Also the perfect size for anything and everything.
Love him.
So this is what I'm calling my fashion week look.
I am wearing a vintage Dolce & Gabbana dress, which I love, it's very comfortable and
stretchy.
So I can get in and out of buildings, in and out of cars, go
to shoots and shows and feel really comfortable and not feel like I'm really constrained.
I actually feel really good in this dress.
These are vintage Gucci boots.
They're just a good find.
I love them.
You'll probably see me in these boots all the time.
This Theroux bag is, again, just a good basic.
I'm obsessed with her.
And then, once again, a vintage Gucci sunglass.
These you will catch me in every single day.
And this is kind of my vibe.
A little Italian designer in Italy.
Milan Fashion Week.
I can see it now.
Sorry.
OK.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
So this is kind of my going to work, going to set, going to a
meeting look.
This is kind of my everyday.
I'd say this is a uniform for me.
Again, a t-shirt.
This one's white and a pair of jeans.
And then I like to kind of throw something special on.
So I feel like I'll throw...
this coat, which is the row, shocker.
That's all I wear.
But I love it.
Just a good classic trench.
I am absolutely obsessed with it.
It's a coat I can wear in the spring, so I love my row coat.
This is another Sunday Best tee.
This one's in white.
They're so good and stretchy and kind of a thicker fabric.
These jeans, again, are Kate.
They're the exact black jean that I had on earlier.
I will never get sick of these jeans.
Like I said before, best fit ever.
Love them.
And then my boots are also my ultimate favorite.
These are the Roe as well.
They're a take on a riding boot and I am a horse girl.
So I love these boots a lot.
They feel like me.
I feel like if I was a boot, this is what I would be.
I'm adding sunglasses because like I said, I can't leave the house or the hotel
without them.
So these are also vintage Gucci.
I guess I have a common theme.
I have a lot of vintage Gucci sunglasses, but they are just really great.
And then last but not least, I'm adding a bag.
This is also the Rowe, my queen's.
Just a really good bag to add a pop of color.
Doing business in this, cracking big deals.
So this is my airport look.
I love to be comfortable on a plane so don't get it twisted.
I am not wearing these jeans on the airplane.
I always have a pair of leggings in my carry-on that I carry with me
everywhere so that I can roll up in style and then change into my leggings
on the actual plane.
So yeah, I'd say this is my airport look.
This is a Ralph Lauren jacket from 2018, vintage tee.
These are some Levi 501s.
I think these were men's.
They were huge on me when I got them and I tailored them to fit
me.
Just once again, I can't ever really find a jean that's long enough for me
unless they're probably men's or they're the Kate jean.
So these are Levi's 501s and then these are row boots.
They're a bit high.
They go up to the knee but have a small little heel, which is my
favorite because it's just comfortable.
And this is kind of me.
I'd probably actually wear it zipped up, I'd say.
zipping her up i think that's a little better and then once again
sunglasses this is me to the
airport i go
so
this is my vacation look um i am wearing a pair of row slouchy flowy
pants so i don't really know what they're called but they're super comfortable um a
little bra top and a boatie shirt i love this shirt it's so pretty i'd
probably add a good bag i love this boatie bag keeping in theme with my
Bodhi shirt.
This bag was a birthday gift.
I love it very much.
It's just good.
I love having like a big sack bag for the beach or just to be
able to throw all my stuff in, some books and some sunscreen.
And yeah, but I love this bag.
It's personalized to me and my life.
This is my dog and my horse.
His name's Arizona.
My car, some favorite places I've been.
Kung Fu Kenny is what my friends call me.
It's a lot of me on this bag.
So I love it so much.
And it's very big.
It's the perfect size for vacation.
So I'd say this is my vacation vibe.
Cool.
So this is my night out look, birthday party look, whatever you want to call
it.
I love to be really, really comfortable when I go out, but also feel really
cute.
And
sexy, I guess.
I like to have something very form-fitting, so that's why I love this dress.
Love a little snatched waist.
The whole look is Bottega, so literally from ears to toes, I am in all
Bottega.
Bottega earrings, Bottega dress, Bottega shoes.
I love Bottega right now.
They're one of my favorite Italian designers, so super happy to always be wearing them.
I wore a version of this dress to the U.S.
Open last year.
It was in a pastel yellow.
This is a little black silky one.
I love the fit of this dress.
I think it's super form-fitting and cute.
I work for Forward and I have the privilege of stalking their website at all
times.
And so I got this whole look on Forward, which is really fun.
I love a smaller, small-ish bag when I'm going out at night.
I'd say this is a good one.
This kind of matches my shoes and it's also Bottega to go with the entire
Bottega look.
I feel like this is the vibe.
This is most likely what I would wear on a night out to a birthday
party or a friend's dinner or anything like that.
So I feel very comfortable and I love it.
So if you couldn't guess, this is my workout day.
This is probably what you'll find me in most days of the week.
I am getting up pretty early every morning and hopefully going for a workout.
I usually do Pilates.
That's why I have sambas on rather than a real, you know, proper gym shoe.
But, yeah, this is my going-to-Pilates look, I guess.
I'd add a sweatshirt.
I love this one.
This was actually my dad's sweatshirt.
And it's just super old and cozy and really worn in.
So I love this guy.
This is my going to the gym.
Last but not least, this is the bag you will see me in most in
life.
If you follow me at all, you know that I am wearing this bag probably
every single day.
It is definitely the most worn bag that I own.
It's again the row and it's just a good slouchy tote bag.
Goes with literally everything.
And yeah, this is my, me the majority of the time is this.
Lastly, my sunglasses.
And I'm done.
Thanks Vogue.
I hope you enjoyed watching what I would wear in a week.
To watch more Vogue videos, subscribe here.